(626) 673-3733

LinkedIn.com/in/brandon-sandall

brandsand@gmail.com

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Leader: Drove a 75% YOY increase in revenue by training the team on client relationship management, sales techniques, product knowledge, time management. Got to know each team member to help with our relationship. **Entrepreneurial:** Founded multiple successful businesses. Tasks have included: Find strategic partners, generate proposals for customers and partners, build tech infrastructure, construct all the designs, hire an outstanding team. **Collaborative:** Managed 11 employees to refine the processes, products, work environment, customer relations. Aim to always be open to hear from others to learn and grow from their experience to help all involved accomplish more.

EXPERIENCE

Owner Jul 2016 - Present

AE Solutions

Columbia, SC

- Collaborated with vendors and partners to expand our understanding of the solar industry leading to strengthened core processes and enhanced quality of available products.
- Established monetary management policies and procedures reducing costs by an average of \$1,250 per job.
- Improved customer care 38% by teaching each employee how to communicate more positively and optimistically.
- Formulated product innovation strategies and analyzed opportunities to enter 2 emerging markets across 3 years.
- Presented proposals to obtain funding for resources, alternative staffing and execution plans to achieve desired results.

Account Manager Nov 2015 - Jun 2016

LGCY Power

Columbia, SC

- Earned multiple awards as a top performer out of 200 employees when, in 2016, LGCY was in 15 states.
- Shared sales knowledge with co-workers, increasing office sales by 72% and improving overall performance.
- Received several hundred referrals from previous customers by developing relationships built on trust, honesty, integrity, and respect resulting in an additional \$2.4 MM in revenue.

Owner Sep 2014 - Nov 2015

Rocky Mountain Window Washing

Rexburg, ID

- Founded company to help local businesses and hire college students to assist with tuition expenditures.
- Obtained working contracts of 14 respected companies in one summer in an exceedingly competitive location.
- Developed processes and programs needed to help ensure operations ran smoothly and more profits were realized.
- Managed relationship with over 150 clients; coordinated among employees for projects worth \$240,000.

Customer Service Representative

Jun 2013 - Sep 2014

Apple

Rexburg, ID

- Optimized chat support technology process flows and reduced response time by 30% going from 10 clicks to 7.
- Collected one of three "Star Performer" awards for outstanding performance, given to top 1% employees.
- Received multiple perfect scores on scorecard grading system by going above and beyond on phone calls and chats with customers resulting in a 15% surge in team's average scores.

EDUCATION

Business Management – Finance Emphasis

Graduated September 2019

Brigham Young University – Idaho

Rexburg, ID

• Concentrations: Computer Information Technology, Project Management, Finance.

PERSONAL

- Led and trained a group of up to 40 service volunteers in Arcadia, CA.
- Learned the Spanish language to help the Spanish speaking people of CA understand what was being taught.
- Eagle Scout and volunteer with a religious youth group.
- Technology enthusiast, personal fitness advocate, and lover of outdoor recreational activities.